xplore-tech.com 2015-05-22

# Xplore-Tech Services Pvt Ltd

Xploretech Services is committed to protecting your privacy as well as developing technology for offering you an exceptional online experience. This Statement of Privacy is applicable to the Xploretech Services website and governs data collection and usage. By using Xploretech’s website, you consent to the data practices mentioned in this statement.

### Collecting Personal Information :

Xploretech Services collects personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address, home/work station address, or telephone number. Xploretech also collects anonymous /graphic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, ZIP code, preferences, interests and favorites.

Information is also provided about your computer hardware and software, which is automatically collected by Xploretech Services. These details may include your IP address, browser type, domain names, timings of access, and website addresses for referral. This information is used by Xploretech Services for operations, and for maintaining the quality of service, and for providing general statistics regarding use of the Xploretech website.

Note that if personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data is disclosed by you through Xploretech‘s public message boards, it can be used by others. Keep in mind that Xploretech Services does not read any of your private online communication.

Xploretech Services motivates you in reviewing the privacy statements of websites that you choose to link to from Xploretech, so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Xploretech is not responsible for the privacy statements or any other content on websites outside Xploretech Services’ family of websites.

### Using your Personal Information:

Xploretech Services collects and uses your personal information to operate the Xploretech website and deliver services you have requested for. Xploretech also uses personally identifiable information to inform you of other products/services available from Xploretech and its affiliates. Xploretech Services may also contact you via surveys for conduct research on your opinion about current services or potential new services that might be offered.

Xploretech Services does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Xploretech may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In these cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Xploretech may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except for providing services to Xploretech and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
